https://loradchemical.com/terms/privacy-policy/

Home
Privacy Policy
Privacy Policy
PRIVACY POLICY
THIS PRIVACY POLICY (THE "POLICY") APPLIES TO AND GOVERN YOUR USE OF THIS INTERNET WEBSITE (THE "WEBSITE"), WHICH IS OWNED AND OPERATED BY LORAD CHEMICAL CORPORATION ("LORAD"), ON BEHALF OF ITSELF AND ITS SUCCESSORS, PARENTS, SUBSIDIARES, AFFILIATES, AND RELATED COMPANIES (COLLECTIVELY, THE "COMPANY", "WE", "OUR", OR "US"). PLEASE READ THIS POLICY CAREFULLY, BY ACCESSING OR USING THIS WEBSITE (OTHER THAN TO READ THIS POLICY FOR THE FIRST TIME) YOU ACCEPT AND AGREE TO BE BOUND AND ABIDE BY THIS POLICY, WHICH MAY BE AMENDED FROM TIME TO TIME. SUCH CHANGES ARE EFFECTIVE IMMEDIATELY AND IF YOU USE OR CONTINUE TO ACCESS THIS WEBSITE, AFTER SUCH CHANGES BECOME EFFECTIVE, SUCH USE OR ACCESS WILL SIGNIFY YOUR AGREEMENT TO BE BOUND BY ANY SUCH CHANGES. IF YOU DO NOT AGREE TO BE BOUND BY THIS POLICY, DO NOT ACCESS OR USE THIS WEBSITE.
1. Personal Information You Disclose to Us. We collect personal information that you voluntarily provide us when you submit a quote request, send us a technical inquiry, or otherwise contact us. The personal information we collect depends on the context of your interactions with us and the choices you make and features you use. The personal information may include: (1) your name, (2) your company / organization name, (3) your email address, (4) your phone number, and/or (5) you rphysical address.
2. Information We Collect Automatically. We automatically collect certain information when you visit, use, or navigate the site. This information does not reveal your specific identity (like your name or contact information) but it may include device and usage information, such as your IP address, browser and device characteristics, operating system, language preferences, referring URL, device name, country, location, and which pages you have previously visited on our website. This information is primarily needed for internal analytics and reporting purposes so that we can provide a better more tailored web experience.
3. How Your Information Will Be Used. We do not share any of the information submitted through any form on this WEBSITE except in limited circumstances such as (1) with your consent or (2) to comply with a lawful subpoena from law enforcement or a government agency. Anonymized information that is collected automatically is shared with Google Analytics to help us understand how users are interacting with our website and how we can improve the user experience.
4. Cookies and Other Tracking Technologies. Like many businesses, we collect information through cookies and similar technologies, which you can read about in our cookie policy. We strive to set minimial cookies for a better user experience.
5. Where Your Information is Stored. Our servers are located in the United States. If you are accessing the WEBSITE from outside the United States, please be aware that your information will be transferred to, stored, and processed by us in the United States. If you are a resident in the European Union, the United States may not have data protection and other laws as comprehensive as those in your country. We will however take all necessary measures to protect your personal information in accordance with this privacy policy and applicable laws.
6. Our Stance on Third-Party Websites. LORAD cannot guarantee the safety or privacy of data on any third-party websites that you may find hyperlinked on our WEBSITE. We are not responsible for the content or privacy and security practices of any third parties and you are advised to review the policies of such third parties and contact them directly if you have any questions.
7. How Long We Keep Your Information. We will only keep your information for as long as it is necessary for the purposes set out in our privacy policy, unless a longer retention period is required or permitted by law (such as tax, accounting, or other legal requirements). When we have no ongoing legitimate business need to process your personal information, we will either delete or anonymize it, or, if this is not possible (such as in stored backup archives), then we will securely store your personal information and isolate it from any further processing until deletion is possible.
8. Information Collected About Minors. We do not knowingly solicit data from or market to children under eighteen years of age. By using this WEBSITE you are representing that you are at least eighteen years of age.
9. Controls For Do-Not-Track Features. Most web browsers and some mobile operating systems and mobile applications include a Do-Not-Track ("DNT") feature or setting you can activate to signal your privacy preference nto to have data about your online browsing activities monitored and collected. No uniform technology standard for recognizing and implementing DNT signals has been finalized, as such, we do not currently respond to DNT browser signals or other mechanisms that automatically communicate your choice not to be tracked online.
10. California Resident's Privacy Rights. California Civil Code Section 1798.83, also known as the "Shine The Light" law, permits our users who are California residents to request and obtain from us, once a year and free of charge, information about categories of personal information (if any) we disclosed to third parties for marketing purposes and the names and addresses of any third parties which we may have shared personal information with in the immediately proceding calendar year. If you are a California resident and would like to make such a request, please submit your request in writing to us using the contact information provided below. As of the "Last Update" date, Lorad does not share any personal information with third parties other than anonymized data collected by Google Analytics.
11. Update to this Policy. From time to time, we may update this POLICY. The updated version will be indicated by an updated "Last Updated" date and the updated version will be effective as soon as it is published. We encourage you to review this cookie policy from time to time to be informed of how we are protecting your information.
If you have any questions or concerns regarding our Privacy Policy, you may contact Lorad at:
Lorad Chemical CorporationATTN: General Counsel1200 19th Street NorthSt. Petersburg, FL 33713
Last Updated: February 25, 2020
Terms of Quote
Terms of Sale
Terms of Purchase
Website Terms of Use
Cookie Policy
Privacy Policy
Please Note: In order to give you the best website experience, Lorad uses cookies on this website. If you continue to use this website without changing your cookie settings, you are consenting to the use of cookies by Lorad. For information about what we collect and how we use our cookies, please visit our Cookie Policy and Privacy Policy.
I Agree
